{
  "response_code": 0 ,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "easy" ,
      "question": "The Spitfire originated from a racing plane." ,
      "correct_answer": "True" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "medium" ,
      "question": "&quot;I disapprove of what you say, but I will defend to the death your right to say it&quot; is a quote from French philosopher Voltaire." ,
      "correct_answer": "False" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "easy" ,
      "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential motorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963." ,
      "correct_answer": "False" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "easy" ,
      "question": "The United States of America declared their independence from the British Empire on July 4th, 1776." ,
      "correct_answer": "True" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "easy" ,
      "question": "Adolf Hitler was tried at the Nuremberg trials." ,
      "correct_answer": "False" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "easy" ,
      "question": "Kublai Khan is the grandchild of Genghis Khan?" ,
      "correct_answer": "True" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "hard" ,
      "question": "During the Winter War, the amount of Soviet Union soliders that died or went missing was five times more than Finland&#039;s." ,
      "correct_answer": "True" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "easy" ,
      "question": "The French Kingdom helped the United States gain their independence over Great Britain during the Revolutionary War." ,
      "correct_answer": "True" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "medium" ,
      "question": "Sir Issac Newton served as a Member of Parliament, but the only recorded time he spoke was to complain about a draft in the chambers." ,
      "correct_answer": "True" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "category": "History" ,
      "type": "boolean" ,
      "difficulty": "hard" ,
      "question": "The man that shot Alexander Hamilton was named Aaron Burr." ,
      "correct_answer": "True" ,
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
  ]
}